[man and woman laughing]
[man] Didn't you say you had
a surprise for me. honey?
-[man laughing]
-[woman] I do. Come here. then.
-[man] Okay.
-[both laughing]
Here. look at you. I'll film this.
-[woman laughing]
-Just say hi over here.
-[woman] I don't know how to do this.
-You don't know. honey?
[both laughing]
-[man] It's cold here. Let's go inside.
-[woman laughing]
-[man] So cold.
-[woman] Wait!
-Stop!
-[woman grunting. panting]
[tense music playing]
[large object
being dragged across the floor]
[breathing heavily. straining]
-[rubber squeaking against the floor]
-[straining]
[panting]
[grunts]
[straining. panting]
[sirens wailing in the distance]
[panting]
[tense music continues]
[scrubbing]
[panting]
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
[baby crying]
[continues crying]
Did you miss me?
Mommy's here.
-[baby babbling]
-Mommy's always here.
[gentle music playing]
There are things in this life
you'll understand with time.
Other things you'll learn from me.
Just between us.
-[door opens]
-[tense music playing]
-[door closes]
-[footsteps approaching]
Mrs. Elize!
Marcinha? Didn't hear you come in.
-It's 7 a.m. already.
-Really?
-Are you going on a trip?
-What?
-I saw the suitcases. and…
-Ah. yes. Uh. no.
Just dropping off some extra sales.
-Wine bottles.
-And Mr. Marcos?
What about Marcos?
-Should I get his coffee ready?
-Ah. no more questions.
Just please do me a favor.
Take her upstairs to the playroom.
-It's playtime!
-Let's play!
-Go on now.
-Okay.
[baby babbling]
[tense music intensifies]
[music stops]
ELIZE: SHADOWS OF A WOMAN
[ominous music playing]
[grunts]
[music stops]
7 YEARS BEFORE THE CRIME
[Elize breathes deeply]
1. FAIRY TALE
What's wrong?
-Is my hair a little messy?
-Not at all. Still stunning.
Hmm. stunning?
-You're perfect. Sweet Blondie.
-Now I'm perfect?
-Yes. you are.
-[chuckling]
[cell phone vibrating]
-Hmm!
-No.
[Elize chuckles]
Marcos can't come
to the phone right now because he's…
-He's very busy.
-Please stop.
He's busy fucking the love of his life.
-He is. isn't he?
-Oh. really?
-Huh? Yeah. isn't he?
-[chuckles]
-Second round? [chuckles]
-[laughing]
-[breathes deeply]
-[kisses]
-Delicious.
-Mmm.
[cell phone vibrating]
[Marcos] Goddamn it.
-Don't you get it? Marcos is busy.
-Give me the phone.
-He's professing his love--
-Gimme the phone!
And don't get agitated.
I'm fully booked. I'll just go.
Hi honey. I'm in a meeting with my dad.
so be quick.
I'm buried in work. Mm-hmm.
Heading to the airport. got that interview
with the newspaper I told you about.
Yes.
Your husband is on the list
of Brazil's top businessmen. honey!
-[door closes]
-[upbeat music playing]
[chattering]
I like you. What's your name?
Yes!
-Can we do it from behind. baby?
-Uh. Two. please.
-That accent of yours. It's from where?
-It's from São Paulo. girl.
And. so. my accent.
Can you place it or not?
[laughing]
Hey. Girl. I feel like I'm getting
a bit drunk. [chuckles]
-You're drinking because?
-Drinking to forget.
-[cell phone vibrating]
-Well. now. Speak of the devil.
Answer it.
Hell no. Marcos thinks he has so much.
-So. I'll keep him waiting. for now.
-Don't want to give the devil more power.
[both laughing]
-Don't you follow the news?
-What?
Your flirtatious popcorn vendor
is one of the richest men in the country.
-I know. he mentioned it.
-And?
And he's never going to leave his wife.
They have a daughter.
You still haven't learned
that you won't find a husband here?
-That man is a prince.
-What?
He's not a vendor.
He's the prince of popcorn.
[pensive music playing]
-[man] Hey. Kelly!
-Huh?
I was thinking…
You know. you and my daughter
look very similar. [chuckles]
[man laughing]
Oh. thank you.
-Night. Renan. Take care.
-[Marcos] Elize. Are you avoiding me?
-Oh. no.
-I need to talk to you.
-I don't want to talk to you.
-Don't be dramatic.
I've been calling over and over.
You vanished.
-I have a life.
-All this because I'm married?
-I don't care. I can't anymore.
-I have a daughter. I know. I have a wife.
Uh-huh. yeah.
I told you I'm going to admit Joana.
You don't get everything
the way you want or when you want it.
Come here. I have a surprise for you.
[gears clanging]
[Elize] What's this about admitting her?
[Marcos] The psychiatrist suggested it.
[elevator gears creaking]
[squeaking. panting]
[optimistic music playing]
[squeaks]
-You like it?
-[exhales]
Yes.
-It's yours.
-[gasps]
[door opens. closes]
-[door opens. closes]
-[Elize breathes deeply]
No one's ever given me anything.
I want you to be mine. Exclusively.
Believe it.
["Love is a Losing Game"
by Amy Winehouse playing]
[Marcos] Look at Blondie
having a taste of Japanese cuisine.
-So. you like the sushi. babe?
-[laughing]
Ah. Swallowed it.
[both laughing]
[Marcos] I'm gonna film us. look here.
My very sweet honey.
-[helicopter whirring]
-Stop worrying. it's safe.
Up. up. and away!
[Elize cheers]
[Marcos] So. check out this Blondie here.
[indistinct chatter]
-Hmm!
-[chuckles]
Hey!
Ah!
[song continues]
[Elize] Where else are you taking me?
Anywhere you like.
[Marcos] Here we are in Tuscany. everyone.
[cheering]
-Do you like it. honey?
-I love it!
[Marcos] I love you. you know?
Same here.
[ominous sting]
-[gunshot]
-[music ends]
[Marcos] Snooze you lose. Blondie.
But don't worry.
You'll get it. It will happen.
Come. Blondie.
I've never met a woman like her.
[man] Marcos…
-[door closes]
-[birds chirping]
[deer bleating]
[man 1] Oh. there's a deer.
Approach it fully hunched.
Like that.
Okay.
Mark it. Don't feel bad for it.
Hold your breath.
Then a light squeeze.
-[gun fires]
-[deer grunts. whimpers]
So. did I get it?
-[deer grunting]
-It's still alive.
-[deer grunting. panting]
-[ominous music playing]
[man 2] Finish it off. Elize.
[deer grunting. panting]
-[music intensifies]
-[gun fires]
[music stops]
[ominous sting]
[car engine starts]
Go. go. go. go. go.
[pensive music playing]
[man 1] And he said that they noticed
the same thing last week.
The herds must have found
a new place to graze.
just like they did eight years ago.
[man 3] This whole valley
is usually full of deer this time of year.
[man 1] Usually. yeah. but this season…
I could do it.
For real?
Yeah.
It's my kill. I'll skin it.
She's the real deal. hmm?
[crickets chirping]
Got experience hunting. Elize?
No.
[sniffs] I'm learning
to shoot with Marcos.
Yeah. He told me.
Marcos. he mentioned you're a lawyer.
Well. still studying.
-On top of that. I'm a nurse.
-Wow.
I graduated.
I kind of feel like we've crossed paths.
Your face looks familiar. you know?
[Elize] Hmm.
Where did you work. Elize? I'm curious.
What's this?
Am I being interrogated now?
I just want to learn more
about the girl that caught my best friend.
[chuckles]
[Marcos] Heitor.
-This one here.
-[gasps]
-A special privilege. [chuckles]
-Thank you. man.
-[Elize grunts]
-[Marcos] Hey. Blondie. How's it going?
[grunts] Almost there.
[knife cutting]
[friend] Marcos. look.
Her first kill.
[elevator gears clanging]
We are in an elevator.
[Marcos] Mm-hmm.
-[Marcos laughing]
-[Elize screams] Oh. I'm scared!
-Hang on. I have to turn on the lights.
-[chuckles]
-Ay!
-Oh. where are you going?
I don't know.
Watch your step. That's it.
-[Elize chuckles] Hmm.
-[suspenseful music playing]
-Don't move. okay?
-Okay.
Marcos. where are you?
[snake hissing]
[Elize squeaks]
What's this?
What is this. Marcos?
-[chuckles] Her name is Gigi.
-[gasps]
Oh. she's so gorgeous.
I know. right?
-Oh. my God. she's…
-[laughing]
-Oh hi. Gigi. This is Blondie.
-So sweet!
She's so pretty. She's wonderful.
-Yeah.
-Oh. hi.
She likes you. I think.
-She does?
-Mm-hmm.
-Hi there.
-[chuckles]
What is this place?
Our house.
Do you like it?
[Elize gasps]
-Ours?
-Mm-hmm.
[gentle music playing]
[chuckles]
-It has two stories?
-And a pool too.
A sauna.
You like it?
I signed the divorce papers.
I want to marry you.
You'll quit VipClass.
We can even have a baby.
A new life for us.
Just for us.
Forever?
Yes. forever.
[gentle music continues]
[indistinct chatter]
-Hello!
-[Elize] Look at this.
-Isn't this the one you liked?
-[woman] God. I've never used this.
-[Elize] You always wanted to.
-[woman] I used to dream of it.
Wait. you can open it later.
Let me show you this.
[gasps]
Two hundred guests.
-Elize. this is so gorgeous. Amazing.
-[chuckles]
-Wait 'till you see the ring.
-Show!
-Oh. ooh. Look at that!
-[Elize laughing]
[woman] It's so shiny. so pretty.
Pity he couldn't join us here.
I hoped he'd make it.
even insisted. but he's been so busy.
Talk to me.
His family. what are they like?
Oh. his family is nice.
His mother is kind.
Father barely speaks at all.
I don't know much about his brother.
-His cousin's been a friend.
-[chuckles]
-And Marcos…
-[rooster crowing]
Oh. he's been so sweet.
He's fun. you know?
He's like one of us.
You were very lonely. you know?
-Good to have a companion.
-[birds squawking]
And you found someone
that you can start to build a family with.
It's so nice. Hmm!
Very good.
[man] Hey! Give your uncle a hug.
Oh. you look so cute.
-Auntie…
-Easy.
Let's go to the living room. come on.
-That dessert you like.
-[woman] Oh.
-There's extra to take…
-[woman] Thank you so much.
I don't know why. but I'm so hungry.
-Hi. honey.
-Hi. Mom.
Do you want my blessing?
-Bless me?
-May God bless you.
So pretty. You look different.
Hey. Dri!
-Oh. Auntie! How I missed you!
-Sweetie. it's been so long.
I missed you too. Wanna see my new car?
-Our aunt has a big car now.
-So fancy!
[man] You look so pretty.
-Look at you.
-[tense music playing]
Let's look at this glove.
-Will my hand fit? It does.
-Coming. Auntie?
Look at that.
[Elize] Nena.
come see my car. okay? Come on.
Hi. Elize.
[footsteps receding]
[music fades]
[man] Elize.
[knife cutting]
Excuse me.
-[birds chirping]
-[water pouring]
[man exhales]
Is that big car outside yours. Elize?
Figure you must have
really gone and worked…
hard for something like that. huh?
[tense music playing]
[man slurping]
[man exhales]
Well.
Congratulations. honey.
Don't you even think
about coming near me again. got it?
Hey. baby…
If I find out
you did something to any of them.
I'll cut that shrimp dick right off.
-You like it. don't ya?
-Don't laugh!
Put it down.
-Just put it down.
-What's going on? Are you crazy?
She's deranged. totally deranged.
A lunatic.
[music fades]
Mom… [panting]
I told you already.
We don't ever want to see you here again.
Elize. what do you want?
Do you want to ruin my marriage for good?
[dramatic music playing]
[panting]
[crying]
[car beeps]
-[panting. crying]
-[music stops]
-[screams]
-[camera flash charging]
["Love on the Brain" by Rihanna playing]
♪ And you got me like. oh… ♪
-You're so gorgeous.
-Love you so much.
And I love you.
[Elize] I. Elize…
-[priest] Promise to love you…
-[Elize] …promise to love you…
-[priest] …and to respect you. Marcos…
-[Elize] …and to respect you. Marcos…
[priest] …for the rest of my life.
…for the rest of my life.
[Marcos] I. Marcos…
-[priest] Promise to love you…
-[Marcos] …promise to love you…
-[priest] …and to respect you. Elize…
-[Marcos] …and to respect you. Elize…
-[priest] …for the rest of my life.
-…for the rest of my life.
[song continues]
[camera shutter clicks]
[people clapping. cheering]
♪ Must be love on the brain ♪
-♪ That's got me feeling this way ♪
-♪ Feeling this way ♪
♪ It beats me black and blue
But it fucks me so good ♪
♪ And I can't get enough ♪
♪ Must be love on the brain ♪
-♪ And it keeps cursing my name ♪
-♪ Cursing my name ♪
♪ No matter what I do
I'm no good without you ♪
♪ And I can't get enough ♪
♪ Must be love on the brain ♪
[song ends]
[laughing]
You're Marcos's cousin. right?
And you're from São Paulo?
Correct. São Paulo.
-We're from Chopinzinho.
-I know! [chuckles]
It's so different here.
São Paulo is so lively. isn't it?
You came all by yourself. Marta?
Ah. Mr. Matsunaga. Yeah.
unfortunately. my family couldn't be here.
[Mrs. Matsunaga] Good flight?
Yes. I was a little tense
because I'm not used to flying.
-[chuckles]
-Anyway. congratulations.
Your son looks overjoyed.
Thank you so much.
Thank you so much
for welcoming my niece here
into your family
with such kindness and love.
She's a true gift. you know?
She's my angel.
[Elize chuckles]
Marcos was so quick
to get married to Elize
that I thought
it could mean a grandchild soon.
[laughing]
No. no. Mrs. Matsunaga.
You won't be having children?
No. I will. [chuckles]
I was saying we're not ready to have one.
-Maybe soon.
-[laughing]
But Elize has always wanted
the chance to be a mother.
[Elize] We really want to have a baby.
-[both moan]
-[Marta] Aw! [chuckles]
-I was just telling Lauro…
-Ah. no. Heitor!
-No. wait. Come on now.
-Let me talk to your father.
You are finally
gonna pretend to be serious?
Well. Marcos did skip
over the halftime break.
You jumped straight
into the second half. Marcos!
[woman] Heitor!
Well. Marcos doesn't always follow
counsel from the family.
-That's true.
-Right. Pa?
Yeah.
Second time he's been married.
This time has to work out. right. Eliza?
"Lize". it's Elize. yes?
-Yes.
-Ah. Elize.
It'll work out. It'll work out.
Here's to the newlyweds.
Let's raise a glass for them.
Yes. cheers!
-[Marcos] Oh. no!
-No. you can't say "cheers".
-[all] It's "kanpai".
-Kanpai!
Excuse me. Elize. I have someone
I'd like to introduce to you. Mr. Alberto.
-[ominous sting]
-Marcos is a very lucky guy.
Hey. Kelly! You know.
you and my daughter look very similar.
-And this is Luisa. his daughter.
-All the best.
-Thank you.
-Uncle Takashi is in the other hall.
-Let's go. [laughing]
-Coming.
[tense music playing]
-[panting]
-[people chattering. laughing]
-Your hands are cold. What's wrong?
-Nothing.
[inaudible]
[Marcos]
Come. I want to dance with my wife.
Oh. say that again.
-I want to dance. yeah?
-No. [chuckles]
When you said. "my wife".
You are completely my wife.
-Hmm!
-[chuckles]
-[screams. laughing]
-[laughing]
-[Marcos humming]
-[Elize laughing]
["Your Love Is Everything"
by Geoff Gascoyne playing on the speakers]
♪ You're always on my mind ♪
♪ So don't waste precious time ♪
[sighs]
♪ And give your love to me
It's easy ♪
♪ Your love is good for me ♪
♪ It's true ♪
♪ That I am helpless without you ♪
[suspenseful music playing]
My collection is all yours as well.
[Elize] Mmm.
Oh. you're such a badass. yeah?
Undress.
-Okay.
-[clothes unzipping]
I like that.
[chuckles]
[both panting. moaning]
-[music stops]
-[elevator gears clanging]
3 YEARS BEFORE THE CRIME
There was this lady
in the row behind me on the plane. Argh.
2. SANDCASTLE
She went on and on for the entire flight.
Oh. my God. Elize.
This is my house. Auntie.
And our pool. you see. is there. upstairs.
-[gasps]
-And this view.
Wow. to keep it clean
must be a lot of work.
[Elize] Yeah.
I'm so happy you came to visit us.
And Marcos is happy as well.
I'd get lost in this maze of a mansion.
-Ah. you'll get used to it.
-Hello. Ms. Marta.
Oh. Marcos. How are you?
-Doing well?
-Doing well. Very well.
And Elize has been super excited
to have you over.
Beautiful house that you have here.
Please make yourself at home
while you're here.
But. sadly. I can't stay.
-What?
-I'm going to Brasília. Remember?
-You didn't tell me you were traveling.
-I did.
-No. my love. you didn't.
-I did. You're confused.
No. I'm not just confused.
We have the doctor tomorrow.
It's your doctor appointment. not mine.
Not for me.
You are the one having trouble.
[melancholic music playing]
[Marcos] Is this gynecologist any good?
The best in São Paulo.
Yeah. for some. getting pregnant
might take more time. It's natural.
Ah! Auntie Marta can go with you then.
Yes. I'd be happy to join.
[Marcos] Thank you. Make yourself at home.
[suitcase wheels rolling away]
So. when will you get back?
[Marcos] In about two or three days.
I think. I'll let you know.
[keys jangling]
[door opens]
-I'm gonna wash up for now.
-[door closes]
Then we'll get something to eat.
[suspenseful music playing]
Auntie? Let's…
This is our pet snake. Gigi.
Now. wouldn't you rather
get a dog or a cat or…
Oh. she's very tame.
It's a bad idea
to keep a snake with a child in the house.
Marcos said he will buy two dogs
once our baby gets here.
But get rid of the snake
or it will eat the dogs and the child.
-[intercom ringing]
-Oh boy! That must be our pizza.
[suspenseful music playing]
Oh. I killed that.
Why?
For the meat.
I didn't expect you to be into that stuff.
Well. we are.
Is that why you have
a full closet of weapons?
What did you assume it was for?
I don't know.
-I learned from you.
-Huh?
I remember killing a chicken
at your house.
I was around ten years old. I think.
First try. do you remember?
Well. it's completely different to butcher
a chicken and murder this large animal.
They're both animals though.
Elize?
Hmm?
About this treatment.
Do you think it'll work?
Why are you asking me this?
[exhales] He is a man.
They're not great
about most things that take time.
[tense music playing]
[Elize] Three months and nothing.
[doctor] Your body is responding
very well to the treatments.
Your tests are great.
Now. we just need your husband's tests.
[inhales sharply]
Marcos has a daughter
from his first marriage.
-The problem is me.
-[doctor] That doesn't mean anything.
His levels can be affected by his age.
Without your husband's tests.
it could be difficult to continue--
[Elize] Let's just continue.
I can take it.
[pensive music playing]
-[Marcos panting. moaning]
-[music continues]
[Marcos grunts]
-[music fades]
-[birds chipping]
[upbeat music playing]
[Heitor] Look at this one.
[Marcos] It's unreal.
Have you had a taste? Delicious.
Does she know?
[exhales] Oh. Heitor was just showing me
the latest lots of Cuban cigars.
Auction just got posted.
The cases shown
had starting bids at a hundred grand.
You married a proficient businessman
with a keen eye.
He invests only in premium things.
That make a good return.
[footsteps approaching]
[woman] Heitor?
Ah. Bianca!
My last-minute special guest of honor.
Welcome.
These are my friends. Marcos and Elize.
How are you doing?
Hmm.
[Heitor] Hey.
would you like a glass of whiskey?
[Bianca] Yes. please.
[water pouring]
-[footsteps approaching]
-[Bianca] Elize?
-Elize?
-He mention me. Lari?
-Does Heitor know who I was?
-He doesn't know about you.
-You met each other how?
-Through VIPClass.
-Logged on the site. offered to pay cash.
-And Marcos? Had you met Marcos?
I don't know Marcos.
I didn't know you guys would be here.
[exhales]
Are you okay?
Mm-hmm.
You disappeared.
You look really beautiful.
I told you you'd become
"Princess of Popcorn."
Yeah. I married Marcos.
I feel great.
-Ah. but you've had better skin.
-[chuckles]
We're trying to get pregnant.
I'm so glad to see you like this. Happy.
And your safe. all right?
I don't know you.
Eliza. right?
[footsteps walking away]
[breathes deeply]
It was our secret.
I've been exposed.
I've been humiliated
in front of that… unbelievable creep.
[Marcos] I didn't mean to.
When did he find out?
-What if he told your parents?
-Crap.
Jesus.
This treatment is making you neurotic.
You stopped drinking
and you're getting paranoid.
-[door opens]
-[water running]
-[computer chimes]
-[suspenseful music playing]
[water stops]
[clicks tongue]
[toilet flushes]
Calmed down yet?
-Mm-hmm.
-Honey.
Can you please pick this stuff up?
I have to reply to Lauro's email.
[typing]
Hmm. You've worked enough.
-[suspenseful music continues]
-[typing]
WELCOME
HELLO. WHORE RIDER!
GOOD TO HAVE YOU BACK.
YOUR REVIEW IS UP!
[snoring]
HIGH-END ESCORTS
YOUR REVIEWS
PROFILE: 39 YEARS OLD. ASIAN. MARRIED
STATUS: VIPCLASS DIAMOND
LAST VISIT: 1 DAY AGO
YOUR REVIEWS
1 DAY AGO
WONDERFUL WOMAN
I LEFT WITH A SMILE ON MY FACE
[music intensifies]
[Marcos] We did it twice.
The first time around she rode me.
I started off by treating myself.
going down on her.
She has the body of a model.
A classy lady.
She had a tan mark. She sucks really good.
I finished once in her mouth
and once in her pussy while she rode me.
She likes to fuck. She was beautiful.
skinny. truly a sight to behold.
Very sexy. We did missionary…
Blow job… Very satisfied.
I'll definitely be back for more.
-[music fades]
-[breathing shakily]
[pensive music playing]
[screams]
Blondie! What are you doing?
[music fades]
Are you crazy?
-I read it all.
-Read what?
Your profile on VIPClass.
And that was the auction
you mentioned. is it true?
You went through my stuff?
Did you comment about her tan line?
-What?
-The nymphet you like?
Seriously! Aimed right at her…
her little mouth.
Hey! Why did you go through my stuff?
-Why?
-Yeah.
You promised you'd be different.
I believed you.
-So. I made an error.
-An error. huh?
I'm on hormones so I can get pregnant.
and you made an error?
Not one! Two. three!
-Elize. listen to me.
-I won't listen to you!
-Elize.
-Marcos. I give up.
I am done.
And what will you do?
Will you give up the life I gave you?
You're full of shit. Marcos.
I thought you were different.
I wanted a family with you.
[Marcos] That was my plan.
but you're damaged goods.
-You can't give me a child.
-Fuck you. Marcos! Enough!
I decide when is enough. yeah?
You don't control me!
I love you. Elize.
-I promise I'll change and…
-[retching]
[panting]
[low dramatic music playing]
Are you pregnant?
We did it.
[crying]
-[sobbing]
-I'll take care of us. okay?
[music becomes sentimental]
Will you forgive me?
[heart beating]
THAT MAKES MY NEW LIFE BLOSSOM…
…WITH EVERY GESTURE…
AND REVEALS…
♪ Twinkle. twinkle. little star ♪
♪ How I wonder what you are ♪
♪ Up above the world so high ♪
♪ Like a diamond in the sky ♪
♪ Twinkle. twinkle. little star…♪
-[baby crying]
-[music fades]
She's hungry. probably.
What's with the suitcase?
I have work in Curitiba. I have to go.
You said
you were having lunch with me today.
Change of plans. though.
Do you have to go? To do what?
Company stuff.
You know everyone's involved in this sale.
My father's hounding me.
You swore you'd change for us.
-What are you talking about?
-You've lied straight to my face.
When will you let this go?
I just won't.
I can't handle it anymore. Marcos.
-Not one more time. Say it!
-Elize. seriously…
Find yourself some psychiatrist.
You're crazy. Get some new medication.
You're paranoid.
-I'm not paranoid!
-Then stop acting crazy. will you?
[suspenseful music playing]
-[shushing baby]
-[baby whimpering]
-Calm down. It's okay. [shushing]
-[baby crying]
Calm. baby. Calm. [shushing]
[music stops]
You sure you don't want to go for a walk?
Thanks. but Marcos
should be back from his trip.
and we have been missing Daddy.
-Haven't you been missing your papa?
-[cell phone ringing]
There he is. Ah.
Hey. Marcos.
We were just talking about you.
Clarice is here too.
Do I have to?
Here. Marcos would like to speak with you.
Hi. cousin.
See? Told you I've been home all day.
-What?
-[baby babbling]
Okay. Talk soon. [sighs]
-What is it?
-A meeting started late.
He'll be back tomorrow.
Your papa will be back tomorrow. okay?
-[Marcinha] Want me to hold her?
-Yes. please. Take her.
-Oh. come here.
-Oh! Wait. wait a moment. sweetheart.
Okay.
-[Elize] Let's go for a walk.
-That's Auntie's little angel.
-[footsteps receding]
-[baby babbling]
[sighs]
Is something going on?
I guess I'm afraid I'm losing Marcos.
Why are you saying that?
It's because I lost so much in my life.
My father cheated a lot on my mom.
Then. one day. he left.
He abandoned us long ago.
Wasn't it for the best he left?
No one gets past that easily.
Then my mom found a guy
worse than my father.
My stepfather.
[melancholic music playing]
I was about 12 when it all started.
And it got worse around 15.
[sniffs. crying]
I said "no" so many times.
I don't want my daughter
to grow up without her father.
I won't just abandon my family. [sniffs]
I struggled so much to prevent that.
That won't happen.
[breathes deeply]
[music fades]
[siren wailing in the distance]
MARCOS 4 HOURS AGO
MY FLIGHT WAS CANCELED. DON'T WAIT UP
My love?
[snoring]
Honey?
-Huh?
-Wanna come to bed?
I'll just sleep right here. [groans]
-Come to bed now.
-I love you.
[snoring softly]
[suspenseful music playing]
[snores. clears throat]
[beep]
I CAN'T WAIT FOR YOU TO…
[Elize] "I can't wait
for you to quit VipClass."
MARCOS: OH. YOU'RE SO HOT
[gasps]
[shower running]
-[shower stops]
-[music fades]
Are you asleep?
Hey. come here.
-[tense music playing]
-[Marcos breathing heavily]
Come on. come here.
[scoffs] Are you really
going to leave me hanging?
-I'm just tired.
-[scoffs]
You used to spend all night taking care
of multiple clients in that club of yours.
And you didn't get tired.
What did you just say?
What? [laughs]
You have a maid. a nanny.
a credit card. a house. a car.
What else do you want?
You can't please your husband
who pays for all this?
I don't want to fight you.
Want me to pay you?
[bills rustling]
A hundred. two hundred.
three hundred. six hundred.
Take it all. Is that enough?
I'm your fucking wife. not your hooker.
I am the mother of your daughter.
That's the problem.
You will abandon me.
-Aw. not this again.
-You made a promise.
You said what happened to your ex-wife
would never happen to me.
-First chance you get. you go back…
-Stop! Shut it!
Look at yourself.
You are hysterical.
With how worried I am right now.
I wouldn't leave my daughter in your care.
See a doctor.
[melancholic music playing]
Crazy bitch.
[gasps]
[door opens. slams]
MENTAL HEALTH
PSYCHIATRIC CLINIC
[Elize] Rehabilitation.
Private room. 680 reais.
Half day. 350 per day.
[voice starts to fade]
Medication. 120 to 450.
[suspenseful music playing]
You've reached Danielle's voicemail.
I can't answer the phone right now.
Leave your message after the beep.
[phone call ends]
[music intensifies]
[pensive music playing]
[snake hissing]
-[upbeat music playing]
-[people chattering. laughing]
[cell phone chimes]
DANIELLE: WHERE R U BABY?
R U COMING?
[cell phone ringing]
Hello?
Ah. Hello?
Sorry.
-Are you available?
-No. no.
Why aren't you answering?
[Elize] Honey. can I get a martini?
Same for me.
Double. please.
-Celebrating?
-I dunno. Just trying to cheer up.
Had a no-show client
and he won't answer calls.
Well. look around the place.
Plenty of gracious clients. honey.
Are you new to this?
More or less. yeah.
I used to come here.
Then I stopped after a while.
Went exclusive.
My fantasy.
-Oh. yeah?
-Uh-huh.
Ah. but it's not difficult. right?
Eh. just avoid the married ones.
Those men are tricky.
It's the married ones I love.
How powerful.
No. I think
it's just so much simpler. you know?
They tend to be
more preoccupied with their wives.
so they're much less
of a pain in the ass for us.
-I have one like that.
-Huh?
A prince. I bet?
[chuckling] More or less. yeah.
He's saying he'll leave his wife
to be with me now.
[ominous sting]
The guy is obsessed with me.
He gives me gifts. takes me on trips.
to dinner at Japanese restaurants.
taught me about wine.
In his case. I kinda get it.
His wife is kind of…
out of her mind.
-[glasses clink]
-[Danielle] Cheers!
It's on the level
of psychiatric clinics. medication…
He's having her admitted next week.
[ominous music playing]
[camera shutter clicking]
[music fades]
Well?
So. he's still in there with her.
Look. This is from when they arrived.
Each in their own car.
And look closely. you'll see.
Her car is just like yours.
same color even.
-They've been there for about two hours.
-I knew it.
I took pictures too. The whole package.
Your lawyer will love it. huh?
-Mrs. Elize. this is…
-Go away.
Send me everything. Go!
Of course.
-[tense music playing]
-[door opens. closes]
[music fades]
18 HOURS AFTER THE CRIME
[suspenseful music playing]
3. EYE OF THE STORM
[car beeps]
[metal clanging in the background]
[panting. grunting]
[breathing heavily]
[cell phone dialing]
Hi Marcinha. How are you?
Listen. I went out for a bit.
How's my little girl?
[Marcinha] She's a little warm.
She has a fever of a 100ºF.
Can I give her the usual medicine?
-Sure.
-Twenty drops. right?
Sure. And is Marcos at home?
-No. ma'am.
-Okay. I'll call him. Bye.
[sniffs]
[crying]
-[music fades]
-[birds chirping]
[breathing heavily]
[suspenseful music playing]
[crickets chirping]
[cell phone ringing]
Hi. Marcinha. How are things?
-[Marcinha] Almost a hundred four degrees.
-A hundred and four?
-Did you give her a bath?
-I did. I don't know what else to do.
Okay. I'm heading back now. Bye.
[tense music playing]
[siren wailing]
[Elize] Not now.
Please pull over. ma'am.
Good evening. ma'am.
-Good evening.
-This is just a routine check.
-[siren wailing]
-[chatter over the police radio]
[tense music continues]
What's the matter? Are you nervous. ma'am?
No.
It's just that I really need
to get home soon.
See. my baby has a high fever.
Could you possibly let me go
just this once?
License and registration.
I'll be right back.
The car's registration is expired.
Ask your husband to take care of that.
Okay. You're free to go.
-Hey. stop. You two. Stop!
-Good night. officer. Thanks.
You there!
Pull over. pull over. pull over.
[thunder cracking]
[tense music continues]
[panting]
[straining]
[cell phone ringing]
HAS THE FEVER GONE DOWN?
[panting. straining]
[animal growling]
[dog barking]
[grunts]
[whispering] That scared me.
-[ominous sting]
-[music fades]
[man] It's been two days
since I last heard from him.
Mm-hmm. Let me know
if you hear anything. Thanks.
[water pouring]
I know you're feeling nervous.
dear. but try to remember.
For his sake. try.
[breathes deeply]
I already told you all I remember.
Try to stay calm and really think back.
See. even the smallest detail
could be of help.
I woke up when I heard him
moving all his things around.
[Heitor] What things?
Well. like a bag. a carry-on.
[suspenseful music playing]
Some shirts and pants.
His cash. laptop. and his cell phone.
He had to be kidnapped.
-Don't even say that.
-[gasps]
[man] Marcos disappears
the week of the company selling?
-It isn't a coincidence.
-Why hasn't anyone contacted us?
[Mrs. Matsunaga] Are you sure he didn't
say anything else before he left?
He said he wouldn't be back until later.
That he might not be back.
He leaned over on the bed… [groans]
…and kissed my head.
He said. "A man has to do
what a man has to do."
I just want him to be okay. that's all.
It's okay.
[doorbell rings]
-That should be the police.
-[Elize gasps]
[door opens]
[Mrs. Matsunaga] He'll turn up.
Marcos will be all right.
Yeah.
-There must be an explanation.
-[officer] Hello.
If you need something.
you know I'm around.
I know that.
Don't forget.
Thank you.
[officer] Stay calm.
There's still time.
He hasn't seemed to reach out yet.
but we're tracking everything. and we…
This is Clarice.
-How are you?
-Hello.
Elize. She's Marcos' wife.
-Good afternoon.
[sniffs] Heard anything yet?
Chief Aquino was explaining that
they're distributing a photo of Marcos
and contacting other police stations.
as well as hospitals.
[woman] And the anti-kidnapping unit
will track any call asking for ransom.
-[beep]
-[ominous music playing]
[reporter on TV] A dark enigma.
Fragments of a body
were left on the side of dirt roads
near the city of São Paulo.
more precisely
in the district of Caucaia do Alto.
a rural area of Cotia.
In a case that borders on the macabre.
near the side of a dirt road.
a single leg was found
inside a blue trash bag.
Civil Guard agents found
the other missing limb.
The search for the mysterious
missing body parts continues.
Hands. arms. and the head.
Crucial pieces to solve this mystery…
[music fades]
[baby babbling]
[man] The police will let us know
if there are any developments.
-We can't wait. It's been nine days.
-[Heitor] It's very strange. Marcos…
He sent an email. made a deposit.
but won't answer his phone?
Doesn't make sense.
It seems there was some major activity
at the bank by Marcos.
He deposited a very large sum.
Fifteen thousand reais.
at a bank branch in Vila Brasilândia.
Vila Brasilândia is
by the church we always go to.
What about the email?
It was sent from Marcos' laptop. it seems.
The police will track the IP to find out
where he was when he sent the email.
That's something they can do?
Apparently. yes.
Then he simply wasn't kidnapped.
Oh. Marcos is fine.
Consider it "mother's intuition."
[suspenseful music playing]
[breathing heavily]
[glass shatters]
[Mrs. Matsunaga screams] No!
Now. new blue trash bags
have been found in the Cotia region.
This time. the body parts in the bags
were an arm and the head
of a male victim of Japanese descent.
-Yeah. we're watching.
-With legs. torso. and hips still missing.
Do they know who it is?
-Not yet.
-The police force leading the…
-Calm. Auntie.
-It's not him. Not my son.
-No. it isn't.
-Sit down.
-[moans]
[reporter] …they weren't
as well-preserved as expected.
-[Mrs. Matsunaga moans]
-Deep breath.
[reporter] The head that was found could
significantly advance the investigation.
[tense music playing]
Mrs. Elize.
What?
It's about Mr. Marcos.
[reporter 2] The identity of the victim
of the brutal crime
that shocked the nation
has been confirmed.
His name was Marcos Matsunaga.
Businessman and heir
to a billion-dollar empire.
The murder happened 16 days ago.
It was unclear whether the homicide
is related to the company's sale.
Bags with body parts were found all around
on dirt roads in the Cotia area.
-Now identified. the family awaits…
-[doorbell rings]
I'll get it. Just take her upstairs.
[reporter 2] We'll be back in a bit
with more information.
-[baby babbling]
-[doorbell rings]
[Elize] Go. Go.
Uh. chief?
[Chief] May we come in?
Of course.
Something wrong?
You answer that for me.
Is there something new about Marcos?
Please stay calm now. We just came
to collect some of his belongings.
[Chief] That's okay. right?
Mm-hmm.
[tense music continues]
Are you sure?
We still have to test the DNA.
[Elize] What's that for?
[Chief] Standard procedure.
[camera shutter clicks]
Better come with me
down to the station now.
[music fades]
[Chief] We're recording. okay?
[camera beeps]
Okay.
Your complete name. if you will.
Elize Araújo Kitano Matsunaga.
Marital status?
Widowed?
[Chief] What?
A widow.
Well. now. right?
That was the last time Marcos was seen.
A mistake?
Mistake?
Mistake in the system?
Maybe he took the stairs.
Did he take the stairs frequently?
That's a long way down. wouldn't you say?
What were you carrying there?
[Elize] Nothing important.
Some wines.
Too much wine. right?
-Heavy?
-[Elize] We sold rare wines.
You came back hours after that.
without the suitcases.
Did you sell them too?
I let the customer take them.
Where is your client located?
In urban São Paulo?
No.
They're much closer to Cotia.
[Chief] Hmm.
Could you tell me the customer's name?
Yeah. sure.
-But I don't remember.
-It's okay. Elize.
Fuck. Can't remember
the name of the client?
No. I can't recall.
But I can check.
[lawyer] My client
already answered your question.
Think about your daughter here.
My daughter? Why is that?
You wanna be able to see her again?
Are you making threats?
-I don't get this.
-[Chief] I'm trying to help you.
By taking a daughter away from her mother?
-[Chief] I didn't say that.
-[lawyer] Detective. please.
Marcos was just like you.
He wanted my daughter kept away from me.
[sniffs] Is there anything worse
than taking a child from her mother?
[crying]
I always loved Marcos.
He promised me that he'd be different.
Confess. Elize.
Confess.
[tense music continues]
[sobs. sniffs]
[crying]
-[birds chirping]
-[insects buzzing]
DAY OF THE CRIME
4. THE ABYSS
-[cow mooing]
-[children laughing]
Elize.
Sweetheart. be safe.
and don't burn everything
that you fought so steadily to protect.
Control your anger
and forget this crazy divorce idea.
-I'll make us coffee.
-[cell phone ringing]
-Ms. Camila?
-Hey. Elize.
So. any news?
There is a risk that the court
will grant custody of the baby to Marcos.
He comes from an influential family.
You have a past in prostitution.
Who do you think the court will side with?
What about the photos?
And the video of him with that whore?
Adultery doesn't affect custody decisions.
The alimony will be proportional
to his paycheck.
and Marcos has reported a low income.
-Elize?
-[man] What a beautiful baby.
[tense music playing]
Back off! Don't touch her. motherfucker!
-Get off! Son of a bitch. I'll kill you!
-Get off me. you crazy bitch!
You won't get to touch another little girl
in any way ever again.
-[Marta] Enough!
-I'm going to murder you. you bastard!
-[Elize] Let go of me!
-Are you out of your mind?
Don't try to touch my daughter ever again!
[baby crying]
You come back here
every time. right. Elize?
You like to provoke me. right?
[music fades]
Did you tell Marcos?
[Elize] I did.
He'll pick us up at the airport.
Are you sure
you don't want to spend the night here?
It's all right now. Auntie.
It's past now.
[ominous sting]
-What's wrong?
-Nothing.
It's not my fault the flight was delayed.
Shall I put her to bed?
Not yet. Don't you want
to play with your daughter?
I still have some work calls to make.
[scoffs] Go on. take her.
-Can you take everything to her room?
-Mm-hmm. Of course.
[baby babbling]
-Your job needs you at this hour?
-[intercom ringing]
Must be the pizza. Go and pick it up.
You go then. And make
all your little calls while you're at it.
[Marcos sighs]
Spent all my time caring
for your daughter this weekend.
I'm too exhausted.
I'm not going downstairs.
Then don't.
You can let the pizza get cold.
-Great idea. Good. cold pizza.
-Mm-hmm.
Hey. what have I done? Huh. Marcos?
Tell me before I lose my mind entirely.
You just can't be happy.
-Me?
-I give you the moon.
-What more do you need?
-You. Here.
The only thing I'm missing is you. Marcos.
[dramatic music playing]
[scoffs]
But I have to work. It's my company!
It's your father's company.
Everyone knows you slack off.
Your brother is the one who works.
Don't take it out on me
because your old man doesn't love you.
Shut up. okay?
[intercom ringing]
This fucking pizza.
[door opens. closes]
[suspenseful music playing]
Mrs. Elize?
Are you doing okay?
Yeah.
She's already asleep.
Would you like for me to spend the night?
No.
Are you sure? I can stay and help you.
You can go.
I'll be here early tomorrow. okay?
-Call me if you need anything.
-Okay.
[door opens. closes]
[door closes]
[music continues]
The fuck is this?
Oh. don't you recognize yourself?
You and that stupid whore on TV?
You followed us?
Followed? No.
I hired a detective and you paid for it.
I'm not the one
who can't be happy. Marcos.
You're the one
who can't live like normal people.
You can only get involved
with prostitutes.
So. did you scratch the car?
[chuckles] Are you dumb?
Of course it was me.
You gave her the same
goddamn car you gave to me.
You got the same model.
got the same color.
You took that bitch to the restaurant
we always go to. our restaurant.
I know everybody there.
I know the guy who valeted her car!
What do you think I am?
A plaything with no emotions?
A whore who got lucky
and now is fantasizing she's a housewife.
I am the wife in this house.
The whore is her!
Shut it. Eat your fucking pizza.
And turn that crap off!
I want a divorce.
I'll take my child and be free.
Give her a better example of how to live.
-Better example?
-Uh-huh.
Auntie Hillbilly
or maybe Momma the Fuck-head?
Anyone is better
than a piece of shit ignored by Daddy
who pays prostitutes
because it lets him pretend he's a man.
-Shut up!
-[groans]
[music fades]
[Elize exhales]
That's why Mr. Takashi
is selling the company.
Because he knows
his son is entirely incompetent.
-A coward! You wimp!
-Shut your mouth! You lunatic!
-You always call me crazy!
-My lawyers will take care of you.
-Go ahead!
-You're out of my life!
-Fine!
-Move out of here. whore.
I'm talking to you!
[Marcos] I'm taking my daughter with me!
Now she's your daughter?
[laughing] Put that shit down.
-You don't have the guts.
-[gun cocks]
[laughing]
-Be quiet.
-You're sick. A paranoid bitch.
You know that? [laughing]
Your stepfather was right.
-You've been a whore since you were a kid.
-[gun fires]
-[shell casing hits the floor]
-[Marcos hits the floor]
-[gasps]
-[music stops]
-[breathing shakily]
-[gun clicks]
[phone dialing]
[man] Good evening. This is the police.
-Hello? Is anybody…
-[call disconnects]
[gasps]
[breathing deeply]
[somber music playing]
[Elize laughing on the TV]
[Marcos on the TV]
The natural light makes you glow.
And the view behind you…
-Let's record this. Look. honey.
-[Elize laughing] No. wait.
[Marcos] Beautiful. [chuckles]
-My gorgeous. [chuckles]
-[chuckles]
-Did you really like it?
-I love it.
[Marcos] Tell me the truth. You wouldn't
just tell me that to make me happy. right?
-[Elize laughing]
-[Marcos] You're not lying. right?
You wouldn't do that to me.
[somber music continues]
[knife cutting]
[breathes deeply]
[retches]
-[straining]
-[knife cutting]
[knife hits the floor]
[flesh and bones tearing apart]
[knife cutting flesh]
[knife cutting rapidly]
[grunts]
[bones breaking]
[music continues]
[knife cutting]
[bones breaking]
[music intensifies and fades]
[grunts. panting]
[baby cries in the background]
[baby crying]
Mrs. Elize?
I told you to keep her upstairs. please!
She needs to breastfeed.
Leave her in the crib.
I'll be right there.
Go to the market
and buy what we need for dinner.
Of course.
[shushing]
-[baby crying]
-[music fades]
[Elize shushing] Mmm.
[shushing]
-[baby babbling]
-[kisses]
[shushing]
["O Mundo é um Moinho"
by Badi Assad playing]
[elevator gears clanging]
[song continues]
[camera shutter clicking]
-[man 1 speaking Portuguese] Assassina!
-[clamoring]
[man 2 speaking Portuguese] Piranha!
[sirens wailing]
[Elize in English] I don't know
when you will read this. my dear.
I know there are things
you will never understand.
But there are other things…
Thing that I will tell you one day.
[song continues]
[Elize] But only you.
IN 2016. ELIZE MATSUNAGA
WAS FOUND GUILTY OF MURDERING
AND CONCEALING THE BODY
OF MARCOS KITANO MATSUNAGA.
THE JURY FOUND THAT MARCOS
COULD NOT DEFEND HIMSELF.
THE JURY REJECTED THE CLAIM
THAT THE CRIME WAS MOTIVATED
BY REVENGE OR MONEY.
IN 2019. THE COURT SENTENCED HER
TO 16 YEARS AND 3 MONTHS IN JAIL.
GIVEN HER CONFESSION.
HAVING SERVED 10 YEARS.
ELIZE HAS BEEN ON PAROLE SINCE 2022.
THE MATSUNAGAS WANT TO REMOVE
ELIZE'S LAST NAME FROM THE CHILD.
AND CUT ALL TIES WITH THE MOTHER.
ELIZE NEVER SAW HER DAUGHTER AGAIN.
NOT EVEN IN PHOTOGRAPHS.
[melancholic music playing]
[music ends]
[suspenseful music playing]
[music fades]
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org